london.edu 2014-04-07

# Privacy statement at London Business School

At London Business School, we're committed to providing our community and visitors with websites and services that respect their privacy. 

This privacy statement applies to all London Business School sites and services, but not to external sites. We accept no responsibility for their management and recommend that you read their terms and conditions. 

  * Read the School's Data Protection Policy (PDF document, 74kb)

###  Protecting your privacy 

What information do we collect?  
Cookies  
What do we do with the information we collect?  
How do we keep information secure?  
When do we share information?  
How you can contact us or find out more about privacy and data protection

###  What information do we collect? 

Our sites and services contain online forms that you can use to enquire about or apply for programmes, register for events, download brochures, and donate and pay online via SecureTrading. 

To do this, our sites and services collect a range of information. Much of this is **automatic and anonymous**. 

We will only collect personally identifiable information when we have **your specific consent** to do so. All personal data will be managed in accordance with our obligations under the Data Protection Act 1998. 

###  Cookies 

**What is a cookie?  
** A cookie is a small piece of text information that is sent by an organisation to your computer and stored on the hard drive. **Cookies allow the organisation to recognise you**. 

There are two types of cookie: 

  * **session cookies** last until you leave the site 
  * **persistent cookies** remain on your computer for much longer (how long depends on the specific cookie). 

**Why does London Business School use cookies?**  
We use **Google Analytics** cookies and **WebTrends** cookies to help us analyse how our website is working and make it better. 

We use **login cookies** so that when you log in to restricted areas we can remember your details next time you visit. 

Read on for more details about each type of cookie. 

####  Google Analytics cookies 

####  WebTrends cookies 

####  Login Cookies 

####  Can I reject cookies? 

####  Manage your cookies 

###  What do we do with the information we collect? 

Data we collect automatically is used only to help us measure the effectiveness of our website and plan new developments. This data is processed anonymously. 

**Personal information** is used to give you the information or service you've asked for. We may also tell you about similar products and services provided by the School. 

###  How do we keep information secure? 

We're committed to protecting your data from: 

  * unauthorised access 
  * alteration 
  * disclosure or destruction 
  * accidental loss or destruction 

To do this we have a number of solutions and procedures in place. These are reviewed periodically to make sure they are still effective and meet current best practice. 

The School's Portal is protected by SSL (secure socket layer) technology. However we can't guarantee the security of personal information, in an email or an online form, while it's being transmitted to us across the internet. 

###  When do we share information? 

We don't rent, lease or sell your personal information to third parties. 

There may, however, be times when we share data with third parties to perform specific services. These third parties are not allowed to use your personal information except to provide these services. They are also required to keep your data confidential. 

We may also need to disclose your information if required to do so by law. 

###  How you can contact us or find out more about privacy and data protection 

To make any comments, ask any questions or raise any concerns about our privacy statement, contact us at [help@london.edu](mailto:help@london.edu)

We may update the privacy statement to reflect customer feedback and new legal obligations. To keep informed about how the School is protecting your privacy, we recommend you read this statement periodically. 

For more information on privacy and data protection, visit the [Information Commissioner's Office](http://www.ico.gov.uk/)

Or write to:  
Information Commissioner's Office  
Wycliffe House  
Water Lane  
Wilmslow  
Cheshire  
SK9 5AF  
UK  
Tel: +44 (0)1625 545 700  
Fax: +44 (0)1625 524 510
